

PAWEŁ OSTROMECKI

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I'm a Software Engineer with over 5 year experience at rapidly growing companies. Worked on various projects for Automotive, E-commerce, Manufacturing and Military Industry. Focused on developing efficient, user-friendly web and mobile apps. In brief ambitious, communicative and openminded person.

FEATURES & SKILLS

- Angular 16
- NX Monoreno
- RxJS
- Vue.js 2,3
- Ionic, Capacitor, Android, iOS
- JS, TS, HTML, CSS, SCSS
- SSR (Universal Nuxt)
- PWA
- NgRx, Vuex, Pinia
- Karma, Jest
- Responsive Web Design
- Gitlab CI. Jenkins
- Node.js, Nest.js
- Agile, Scrum
- English B∠
- PostgreSQl
- Supabase

CONTACT

Mobile.: (+48) 661 546 446 e-mail: pawel.ostromecky@gmail.com Wrocław Poland

EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-End Developer (Freelancer)

IT Bees (06.2023 - current)

- Developed functionalities for brand new mobile app Park Control 24
- Integrated native functionalities on Android, iOS (camera, notifications, network etc.)
- Stack: Ionic 7, Capacitor 5, Angular 16

Senior Front-End Developer GOD Nearshore (07.2021 - current)

- Developed and maintained enterprise ERP-class app for automotive industry
- Developed and maintained system consisted of 2 mobile apps created with lonic. Old maintained in lonic 3 + Cordova, new created from scratch with NX, lonic 6, Capacitor 5

Full-Stack Developer

Sendit S. A. (07.2020 - 07.2021)

- Developed and maintained web app for leading polish delivery broker
- Developed backoffice SPA
- Developed map web widget using Vue.js and vanilla JS
- Stack: Angular 12, SSR/PWA, Java Spring, SQL, Gitlab Cl, Docker, SSR, PWA

Front-End Developer

Angry Nerds (01.2020 - 06.2020)

- Maintained app of Spanish airlines operator Volotea booking system, backoffice SPA, landing page
- ERP-class system development for commercial drinkg industry
- Stack: Angular 10+, Umbraco CMS

Junior Software Developer

Exence S. A. (05.2018 - 12.2020)

Software Development and maintenance (Angular 2+, Java Spring, SQL, Node, Nest.js, Electron, Vue) of enterprise apps dedicated for military, energy, manufacturing industries.

EDUCATION

Wrocławska Wyższa Szkoła Informatyki Stosowanej

BSE CS - Bachelor of Science in Engineering (Computer Science)